<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[SIZE IT UP]]></title>
  <link href="http://sizr.net/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sizr.net/"/>
  <updated>2014-07-13T22:59:56+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://sizr.net/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Kartik Luke Singh]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jobspire :: Aspire to find a job you love]]></title>
    <link href="http://sizr.net/blog/2014/03/16/jobspire-aspire-to-find-a-job-you-love/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-16T14:49:12+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://sizr.net/blog/2014/03/16/jobspire-aspire-to-find-a-job-you-love</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We plan to revolutionize the placements system in India. Job satisfaction is not just about the money, its much larger than that. And companies are more than single line descriptions and salary figures. We want to put job seekers in touch with the heart and soul of a company. The people who run it, the place they work and their work culture. We hope to bring about a brighter future and you can help us do it.</p>

<p>You can check out all the details <a href="http://www.blitztheory.com/direct-upload-with-s3_direct_upload/" title="Direct Upload Tutorial by Varun Mayya">here</a>. Do drop us a message if you&rsquo;re interested in helping us move forward.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Limt :: Snapchat meets Dropbox]]></title>
    <link href="http://sizr.net/blog/2012/07/22/limt-snapchat-meets-dropbox/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-22T19:13:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://sizr.net/blog/2012/07/22/limt-snapchat-meets-dropbox</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We recently built an app to that allows you to share files with your friends securely. Just upload a file to our server and select the number of keys you want to create and click GO!.</p>

<p>Each of the created keys takes you to one instance of the file and you can pass these along to whomsoever you would like to send the file too. You also get a key that will help you track the keys you gave out and whether they have expired or not.</p>

<h3>Expiry</h3>

<p>Keys expire thirty seconds after being opened in the case of an image or after a downloaded is completed.</p>

<p>This app was built on the Ruby on Rails platform. One of the biggest problems we faced back at SizrDev was handling large uploads (>100MB) without tying up our own servers or timing out Heroku(which sets itself a 30 second timeout). While going through the options we had in front of us, the team decided to run with a nifty little gem which leverages AWS S3′s new CORS feature in turn allowing us to bypass our server completely and dump files straight to S3. For a deeper look into this look into an article by one of our devs <a href="http://www.blitztheory.com/direct-upload-with-s3_direct_upload/" title="Direct Upload Tutorial by Varun Mayya">here</a>.</p>

<p><strong>Note: Limt is still in development. We&rsquo;re shifting focus to <a href="http://jobspire.net">Jobspire</a> but we plan to finish Limt up soon.</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
